Garry A. Miles Papers
© 2004 University of Connecticut
Garry A. Miles Papers.
undated, 1926-1969.
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center.
Miles, Garry A.
1 linear foot.
Garry A. Miles was an instructor at the University of Connecticut from 1933 (Extension, Asst. Poultryman 1933-?; Instructor, Poultry Husbandry by 1940-1943).
MSS20000145
Biography
Garry A. Miles was born 7 June 1901 and was employed by the University of Connecticut Extension Service in 1933 as an Assistant Poultryman. Over the years, he took on additional responsibilities at the University but was always associated with the Poultry program.
Mr. Miles died in August 1969.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of the personal, daily journal of Garry A. Miles from 1926 through 1969.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged chronologically.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to the University's history. See also, University Memorabilia Collection for Eunice Miles (Class of 1923) materials. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Index Terms
This record series is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Persons:
Miles, Garry A.
Subjects:
Poultry industry--Connecticut.; Puoltry industry--Employees--Connecticut.; Poultry--Study and teaching.; Storrs (Conn.)--Education--Universities and colleges.
Document Types:
Diaries.
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Custodial History
The diaries were found in the barn of Mr. Miles former home by the new owners in 2000 and offered to the University.
Acquisition Information
The collection was donated to the University in October 2000 by Jack and Stacey Fulton.
Detailed Description
- Series I: Diaries, undated, 1926-1969
  - Undated notes (Box 1:, Folder 1)
  - Diaries, 1926, 1936-1937 (Box 1:, Folder 2)
  - Diaries, 1939-1940 (Box 1:, Folder 3)
  - Diaries, 1941-1942 (Box 1:, Folder 4)
  - Diaries, 1943-1944 (Box 1:, Folder 5)
  - Diaries, 1945-1946 (Box 1:, Folder 6)
  - Diaries, 1947-1948 (Box 1:, Folder 7)
  - Diaries, 1949-1950 (Box 1:, Folder 8)
  - Diaries, 1952-1955 (Box 1:, Folder 9)
  - Diaries, 1956-1957 (Box 1:, Folder 10)
  - Diaries, 1958-1959 (Box 1:, Folder 11)
  - Diaries, 1960-1961 (Box 1:, Folder 12)
  - Diaries, 1962-1964 (Box 1:, Folder 13)
  - Diaries, 1965 (Box 1:, Folder 14)
  - Diaries, 1967-1969 (Box 1:, Folder 15)